Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
M_I_SForEver
♪ Every trials and temptations ♪
♪ Is there trouble anywhere? ♪
♪ What a friend we have ♪
♪ In Je... ♪
It's okay, Gus.
It's okay.
It's alright.
That's good. Okay.
Come on, now.
Mama?
Your brother got here
a couple of hours ago.
I told y'all not to come.
And I told you we were gonna.
You don't need to be here.
I know, Mama.
God damn it.
You boys need some help?
Oh, look who's here, Charlie.
It's Superwoman, saving the day.
Hey, pretty.
You taking care of my mama?
Yeah, I'm trying.
I'm glad y'all came out, though.
It's good.
Tried to get here sooner.
Mom looks tired.
Mom looks like shit.
Okay.
Give it here, Charlie.
Food was good tonight.
Mama, I thought y'all weren't
gonna have anymore babies.
Charlie said there's
more than two kid now.
I thought y'all were
just gonna keep the last few.
Doesn't matter.
Your daddy said to keep working.
That's what we do day after day.
It's gonna be okay, Mama.
What's gonna be okay?
I'mma do the dishes.
That was stupid.
Stupid.
Did the doctor say something?
You both know it!
Never listen to me.
Mama...
Go home! Just...
What was that in there?
We deal with things our own way.
- Is that what she was doing?
- I don't know.
What do you want me
to say, Louise?
She'll talk,
if she wants to talk.
Girls are good.
Sorry I didn't call for their...
You're fine.
Becky didn't want them
to miss school.
I think she's worried about
what it might do to 'em,
seeing him this way.
No one likes
So, when was the last time
you talked to him?
They called
for my birthday.
So...
May, I guess.
Last time I saw him,
he was barely there.
How long
you gonna be here?
About a week, I guess.
Friday, maybe.
You still at the post office?
Not... anymore.
We can't leave her
alone out here.
We should've done something.
Hugged her? Something.
Yeah. Yeah.
'Cause that would've made
everything better, probably.
I'm gonna take a shower.
What is it?
It's just the wind.
♪ Every trials and temptations ♪
♪ Is there trouble? ♪
Mama, you should try
and get some sleep, okay?
Y'all should go.
No, ma'am.
It's not... what you think.
What is it?
Mama?
Alright, then.
Mom!
Mom?
Where is she?
Mama!
Mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Mama! Mama!
Hey!
Don't let her fall.
I got you.
No, no.
You sit. You're...
You're alright.
I'm so sorry.
I made y'all some food.
It's a roast.
Thank you.
I didn't want
to say anything before.
It... It wasn't my place.
Your mama...
She was saying things.
Talkin' when she thought
I wasn't listenin'.
I didn't like it.
What did she say?
She would sit...
right beside him
just whispering.
But she wasn't talking to him.
Not like she used to.
It was like...
there was someone else.
Someone here.
I thought it'd be better
with her family close by.
I prayed for them.
She was taking care
of him herself at night.
I can set something up now,
if you want.
It might be better for y'all,
if... if someone was here.
Is there anything we can do.
If we took him to the hospital,
would that change anything?
I'll stay in here overnight.
I can do it.
- If you show me.
- I just think you c...
This is what they wanted.
Go on that other side.
Put 'em in this corner, Charlie.
Wait.
Started bringing
different ones up here.
Had a few certain favorites.
I forgot about Vida.
Who was she talking to?
Don't do that.
It doesn't matter.
She didn't know
what she was doing.
Why would you say that?
She chopped up her own
fuckin' fingers in the kitchen.
She made herself die.
Jesus Christ!
Well, it ain't gonna make sense.
Ever.
We should've talked to her!
Yeah, we didn't!
Hey...
That's okay.
I need three fuckin' minutes.
Michael!
- Dad's in here!
- Louise?!
He wa in there.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Do you want
to talk about it?
No.
I'm gonna go have a cigarette.
I'll come out there with you.
It's stupid.
I feel stupid.
I don't want to talk about it.
I found Mom's diary.
Did you look in it?
I read the last page.
What does it say?
"I know he's there,
in the darkness.
Help me.
Help me, please.
He's killing David.
He can't breathe anymore.
There's nothing
I can do to stop it.
Devil, devil, devil.
He wants...
David's soul."
How'd she get up there?
That cop said the tub,
but you moved it.
What?
She was a couple feet in the air
where we found her.
How'd she get
up there like that?
I don't know.
"The voices in my head...
His voice...
He makes me want to die.
I locked the door,
but he came inside the room.
I want David to wake up.
I grab his hand.
I squeeze it.
- Wake up!"
- Please stop.
"That sound...
so many mouths.
He climbs on the bed.
He hurts David.
- I can hear him."
- Louise!
"I see him.
He...
He laughs at me.
He kills me.
I'm already dead.
I'm dead."
Thank you, Tim.
I know you don't do this,
but we just...
Oh, no, you're fine.
You're fine, Mike.
Thought you might like these.
We found it in her pocket.
What is it?
Those are crosses
they give out in Sunday School.
At least they did
when I was little.
Maybe she collected them.
She... She doesn't.
She... She didn't... go.
You want to get started
on the paperwork?
Yes, please.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Jesus!
Everything alright?
I...
I thought there was a spider.
There was a spider.
Did you get it?
Um...
It was nothing.
I'm gonna get some sleep.
I'm gonna grab some groceries
in the morning.
Goodnight.
♪ What a friend ♪
♪ We have in ♪
I'm sorry.
You have reached a number
that is disconnected,
or is no longer in service.
If you feel you have reached
this recording in error,
please check the number
and try your call again.
Hello?
Told y'all not to come.
Can I help you?
Michael.
Now, I was hoping
we might have a little talk.
You look like your mother.
"I won't know if it's them,
but I hear their voices.
They call.
But what if it's a lie.
He won't stop.
They will die.
We're dead already.
Spiders on my face like tears."
Mm, my, my, my.
Mm.
I started coming to see her.
She was...
She was scared and alone.
I was here for her.
I-I wanted to meet you.
She loves you both so much.
I just thought...
if you like, I can help.
I think you've done enough.
I didn't know about any of this.
This didn't happen overnight.
She had thoughts in her head.
They came from somewhere.
You came to the house.
You were here.
You want to understand, yeah.
She didn't believe in God.
Never did.
None of us do.
My mom thought
the devil was here.
She didn't believe.
What does it matter
whether you believe.
You think the wolf cares
if you believe he's a wolf?
Hmm?
Not if he finds you
alone in the woods.
What did you say to her?
I told her the... the truth.
No, you told her your truth.
Well, maybe so.
Yeah, well, then I guess
the same could be said
about you and yours.
I think you need to go.
- Michael.
- This isn't helping us.
I didn't want to upset you.
Well, you do,
and I'm not gonna sit here
and pretend like
you didn't feed her this shit.
She needed someone.
I think you both
know that now, hmm?
She was alone.
They both were.
I didn't do that.
I helped.
Did you?
Yes. I did.
- How's your father?
- He's fine.
Well, that's good.
I think about him a lot.
You really think
the devil's out there?
That's your truth?
Your mama died, hmm.
You heard her words,
her warning.
You think she's crazy
because she saw a wolf,
saw him coming?
He's not out there.
He's already here.
I don't know
what she wants to do.
I can't tell.
The whole thing's so fucked.
I just want to come home.
Mom was all I had left.
I just miss her.
Oh, no, you stay there.
I told you.
Baby, I walk around here, and...
I don't feel anything.
How are my babies?
Give them a hug for me.
I love you.
"He...
He is...
watching.
He waits.
He is...
everywhere."
Michael?
Hello?
Is someone out there?
She wasn't crazy.
I'm not crazy.
What if she saw something...
out there?
I saw something.
And it wasn't a fuckin' dream.
I wasn't imagining things,
'cause that doesn't happen.
Look at me.
Mom was standing...
right there.
I saw it through the window
last night.
But it wasn't her.
It was fucking scary, Louise.
It can't be real.
There's something out there.
You should come outside.
It's that priest.
The hell?
Come outside.
What are you doing here?
It's like 3:00 in the morning.
Come outside.
You can't just show up here!
Wait.
Don't wait.
You want some rope?
Oh, Jesus.
Michael...
Where'd he fucking go?
He's not out here.
Don't answer it.
Don't!
Come on.
Come on, Michael.
Pick up the phone.
Who's there?!
Alright.
You get out of here.
You don't belong here.
You get, now, come on!
Alright, demon, get.
What do you want?
What do you want?!
Just... Just say it!
You did this to me.
There's no tracks,
no footprints.
Did Charlie ever meet the guy?
Charlie hasn't answered
his phone in two days.
I keep calling.
He was just...
just standing out there,
just waiting for me.
We take dad to a hospital.
We can't keep him here,
not anymore.
We'll get the doctor out here.
You saw his face, didn't you?
You saw it when the...
It can't be real.
Father Thorne?
Who is this?
This is Louise Straker.
We met yesterday.
You came to see us.
Well,
how did you get this number?
You gave it to me.
This is a hotel.
Y-You called my room.
Where are you calling from?
I'm in Thurber.
You were here yesterday.
We met yesterday.
You know my mother.
Thurber? Where is...
You were here.
Thurber.
Thurber, Texas.
I've never been to Texas.
I'm in Chicago.
You don't know Virginia Straker?
Are you trying to be funny?
- But...
- Her name was Louise.
Wait.
I guess
you know that, don't you?
You know I had a daughter.
I don't know how.
Sir, I didn't...
I didn't mean to...
She killed herself...
a long time ago.
Why would you do this?
Sir, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean...
You sound just like her.
Have you, um...
noticed any changes
since you've arrived?
We just want to take him
to a hospital,
so do we need
to fill out some forms
or whatever you need.
I doubt he'd make it
to the highway.
He's getting weaker every day,
and I don't think I can just...
A whole lot has changed.
But I can't sign off
on moving him.
It's just too late for that.
He shouldn't be here.
Is there a problem
with his treatment?
You're not listening.
- I'm trying.
- It's our choice.
And I can't let you kill him.
We just want him safe.
You must see people
at their weakest.
It's got to take a toll on you.
It's not all I see.
There's a lot of love.
It's a silly thing to say,
but it's true.
Sometimes I'm the only one...
when it happens, you know.
I'm just...
the worst thing in the world
to me is...
for a person to die alone.
My mom...
She thought something
was coming for him.
My dad was good.
Michael...
I can see the fear in y'all.
I can feel it in this house.
I know y'all don't
believe in God,
and that's fine...
but I do,
and I think there are
things in this world...
horrible things...
wicked...
...and they come
for whoever they want.
But there's love here.
And a soul needs love
to keep it safe.
I hope you're right.
So do I.
Wolves wouldn't do this...
not this way, not like this.
No.
I'll call another hospital.
Get another doctor
here tomorrow.
She told us not to come.
God damn it!
How many are still out there?
I don't know.
Five, maybe.
We check again in the morning,
but I think we got
what was left.
There was a mama due.
I saw her.
I'm gonna go out there
and sit with them,
- make sure...
- Don't.
Well, I'm not just
gonna let them die.
Not today.
If I'm here, I'm gonna work.
Then let me go with you.
You stay with him.
Please.
I was in there with Dad
earlier today,
and that nurse said something
that's been sticking with me.
There's nothing worse than
a soul left alone in the end.
She wanted me to feel something,
and I wanted to feel something.
Now I just want to forget
about this place.
I'm scared.
Me too.
There you go.
That's a good mama.
Good mama.
Good girl.
You a good girl?
You good girl, mm?
Go on.
Jesus, Becky.
Hello?
Who's out there?
Go on, get!
Go!
♪ Every trials
and temptations ♪
Go away.
♪ Is there trouble anywhere? ♪
♪ What a friend we have
in Jesus ♪
You're not real.
Run away!
Michael?
Hello?
I heard a scream.
I'm okay.
I just...
It's nothing.
I don't know if you remember me.
I'm Charlie's granddaughter.
I was little
the last time I saw you.
We've been calling.
No one answered.
We unplugged the phone.
My mom...
I guess she wanted someone here
to know.
My grandpa died.
He, um...
He shot himself two nights ago.
Wait, I don't understand.
I don't...
Charlie died?
We thought you should know.
I said I'd come out here.
I just...
I thought I'd come and see.
He was here. No.
I just saw him.
That's not possible.
They found him.
I'm sorry about your mama.
You should...
You should come inside.
Do you need help, Louise?
I have to check on Dad.
Come on in.
I just want to check him.
I-I-I'm glad someone's here.
To be honest,
th-th-this morning...
Well, it's just...
do you...
Do you smell him?
I bet you do.
I smell him, too.
He's close now.
He's rotting.
Get away from him!
Get out!
He's rotting.
Get away from him.
All alone.
♪ All alone ♪
Go!
Little girl.
Hello, you've reached
Michael Straker.
Please leave a message,
and I'll call you back.
- Thanks.
- Damn it! Where are you?
We have to get dad outta here.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I told Michael yesterday.
I hope that's okay.
How's your dad doing?
Fuck, fuck. Fuck.
I'm sorry.
Where are you?
I woke up, and you were gone?
I think something
happened to Charlie.
I don't...
Where are you?
I'm driving.
Drove all night.
I wasn't gonna
stay there anymore.
No, no, no, no, wait.
You didn't really leave.
Tell me you didn't,
tell me you didn't.
They need me at home.
Why didn't
you fucking come talk to me?!
I can't believe you did this!
I knew you'd stay.
Damn it!
You left me.
You need to go, Louise.
You're my brother.
You're all I have left.
I love Becky.
I love my girls.
But I'm still here.
They're my life.
What about dad, huh?
You even give a shit about him?
He's gone.
- Listen to me.
- No, he's not!
Listen!
We can't change this.
We don't matter.
Yes, we do!
It won't wait much longer.
Save yourself.
Michael?
Why don't you hear him?!
Listen!
No!
No! Leave!
Jesus...
...you're with me.
I... I hear you.
You're... You're with me.
Jesus...
Jesus, I feel you.
Jesus loves you.
Always there for you.
Becky!
Y'all here?
Hey?
Becky?
Baby?
Girls?
Oh, my God.
My God.
I have to go.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I can't. I can't.
I'm here.
I won't leave you.
Louise!
Michael?!
Are you there?
Louise! Help me!
Help me!
Help me, please! Help me!
Help me! Louise, help me!
Get away!
I love you.
I won't leave you.
Daddy...
Don't leave me.
Daddy!
♪ Every trials and temptations ♪
Mama?
♪ Is there trouble anywhere? ♪
♪ What a friend we have ♪
♪ In Jesus ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org